# ANH-KHOA HUYNH

## SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### CONTACT

+33646398113

khoakun@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anh-khoahuynh-ab8649127/

261 Avenue de la République, Apt 3 59110 La Madeleine, France

### SKILLS

Java · Javascript · HTML · CSS · SQL ChatGPT · JIRA · Postman · Gravitee · Git · Spring · Kubernetes · GitHub · Jenkins · JUnit · Datadog · Vault · Helm · Apache Kafka · Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE) · Google Cloud Platform (GCP) · Hibernate · IntelliJ IDEA · Maven · Docker · Windows · Linux

## EDUCATION

Application developer and designer

### **AFPA Training Center**

2019-2020

Bachelor's Degree - RNCP Level 6

#### **IT Engineer**

### 2i Tech Academy

2021-2022

European Master's IT Expert Intelligent Application and Big Data

-----

## LANGUAGES

French (Native)
English (Fluent)
Vietnamese (Mother tongue)
Spanish (Basic)
Japanese (Begineer)

#### PROFILE

Software engineer with 2 years of experience, people usually call me Anh. I've been working for security payments, retail and supply areas. Currently based in France, I'm willing to travel and am opened to opportunities across the world.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Fullstack developer trainee

#### Worldline

2019-2020 (3 months)

Internal application to manage company's collaborators training wishes.

- Analysis, conception and development of features based on client's needs (product backlog).
- · Testing code and good practices.
- · Bug and application anomalies fixes.
- Improve the ergonomy and application design.

Technologies: Java 8, Vue.JS, MySQL.

# Back-end software engineer

## **Decathlon** 2021-Now (2 years)

Application facilitating data exchanges between AS400 machines and WMS (Warehouse Management System).

- Technical analysis, manage and solving incidents on the application ecosystem (production and preproduction environments). Run, monitoring tools and support requests.
- · Establishment and improvement of data flows traceability.
- Reflection, conception and development of microservices and features based on partners needs.
- · Writing technical documentation according to application evolution.
- Testing application's resilience, clean code and good practices.
- Involvement and contribution during agile rituals (Spring Planning, Retro, Daily Meetings, Demos)
- · Migration of legacy code and application on a Cloud environment.

Technologies: Java 8/11/17 · SQL DB2 · Administration AS400 · ChatGPT · JIRA · API Swagger · API REST · Postman · Gravitee · Git Bash · Spring Boot · Kubernetes · GitHub · GitHub Actions · Jenkins · JUnit · Mockito · Datadog · Vault · Helm · Apache Kafka · Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE) · Code Review · Google Cloud Platform (GCP) · Hibernate · IntelliJ IDEA · Maven · Docker · Agile frameworks (Scrum, Kanban)